% My dreams are all dead and buried %
% Sometimes l wish the sun
would just explode %
% When God comes
and calls me to His kingdom %
% l'll take all you sons of bitches
when l go %
- My turn.
- Hell, no.
- Man, let me drive that thing. Come on!
- Do not touch the trim!
Racial tension has divided
this country for far too long...
and now it threatens to claim
America's favorite animated family.
Santa Claus is dead!
- Your mama's white.
- No, it's a damn lie! l can jump. See?
Cargo slacks are a breeze
at Old Air Force, starting at $14.99.
- No!
- Rusty! Rusty! Be still, boy.
There's only five laps to go, and ol'
Dick Trickle's about to win this sombitch!
Don't let him draft you, dick.
What the?
Hell fire, damn!
- Daddy, l need to know once and for all...
- Oh, damn it, not this again.
l told you, boy, if your mama's white,
then that makes me a damn chalkie lover.
Now, do l look like
a chalkie lover to you?
l don't know, Daddy.
You do drink a lot.
Yes, l do, and l fight.
But some other
crazy sombitch is the one...
what bangulated and pregnified
that white woman. lt's not l!
So you're saying
my mama was white?
- Wait a minute. What did l say?
- You said my mama was white...
and you ain't the crazy sombitch
that bangulated and pregnified her.
Your mama
was a vision in alabaster...
a white lily of the field...
rich with scented pollen
and the sweet odor of the morning mist...
Diet morning mist, actually...
although sometimes she would drink
the regular if they was out of diet.
She was enormous.
Lord, did l love her,
for 32 frenetic seconds.
The loving was good.
- Yeah, l remember that lying whore.
- Don't you talk about my mama like that.
- l mean she lies down a lot.
- l meant the 'whore' part.
- Well, l'll stand by that.
- Bitch.
Russell! You need
to respectify your Aunt Lil.
She ain't some damn dirty-ass whore
that you can trash down, like your mama.
Where my mama's at?
l want to meet her right now!
Well, get back there on the roof.
You can see her fat ass from three states.
That's fine. Yeah,
you just go on ahead and meet her.
Just remember,
l never touched her.
Well, then there's one of me.
Here's one of them, what you call,
them glamour shots and what have you.
What do you know? There's me.
Nope, that's a bus.
Am l in any of these pictures, mama?
Well... Well, look at this one.
l'm about eight months pregnant
with you in this one.
Yeah, l sent that in
to Spank magazine.
Fools rejected it.
You'd print this, wouldn't you?
My daddy said you was
like a huge dollop of sour cream.
- Rich and zesty, with a little bit of bite.
- How is your daddy?
Oh, he's good.
Just got out of prison not too long ago...
No, l'm sorry. Who?
l mean, who's your daddy?
- Anybody l know?
- Early Cuyler?
- Tall guy?
- No.
- Big belly?
- Red hair?
- Not the one.
- Kind of look like Charlie Sheen?
- Not him, neither.
- Or is Charlie Sheen?
- No, not Charlie Sheen.
- ls he a football team?
- No.
ls he the ground keeping crew
for the football team?
- No.
- Are you sure it's not Charlie Sheen?
No, mama! Early Cuyler
is the name. About yea high.
l've been told we look alike,
especially in the eye region.
Same shape of the eyes,
you know, right here?
Well, your daddy, whoever he was...
surely we loved each other
for a period of time.
Of that l am... pretty sure.
Mama, why did you give me up?
Baby doll, it would kill me
to have you to grow up with a mama...
that didn't love you or care for you
or couldn't benefit from you in any way.
- Now do you understand?
- l reckon.
All that matters
is that we're together now, right, mama?
Bring mama a TV.
Son, where do you think
you're taking that demon box?
l got to provide for my mama now.
OK. All right.
You can tell that old fat-ass bitch...
l don't remember nothing
about her, neither!
Did she ask about me?
l asked if she asked about me!
Yep, it's a good life out in nature.
l ain't never having to go back
and forth and in and out.
No EMTs cutting
the doors away out here.
Do white people do anything else...
besides sponge-mop the cracks
in their mamas' back fat?
That's a good question, little thing.
Let's check the TV.
For real, yeah.
l mean, when
black folks use a napkin, they all like...
''Damn! that was some good ribs!''
rub it all over they faces.
And white folks, they all dabbing
the corner of they mouth and...
like they taking some sort of fingerprint.
''What a pleasurable meal!''
Tiger, please.
What a pleasurable meal.
l am a white guy.
- Like that, mama?
- Yeah, son.
Why don't you roll me over, pumpkin?
l feel a sore coming on.
- l told them l couldn't fly a helicopter.
- l told you l ain't moving, Sheriff.
You've got to take me
in dead or alive.
The statute of limitations
passed on that loitering charge.
Congratulations, Krystal.
You've been recognized as a landmark.
What a pleasurable Sheriff.
Rusty, what you doing down here?
Getting a little piece?
l should be outlawed.
You ain't gonna talk about
my mama like that, you son of a bitch!
Mother? How old are you, Rusty?
You about 15?
Give or take, as the crow flies.
Fifteen years ago,
the world was a much different place.
The Berlin Wall had just crumbled.
l thought l could handle cocaine.
l really did.
l lost everything.
And a young deputy sheriff
was learning...
that you can't defy
the laws of love or nature.
l got a report here that says
you won't leave the premises.
Are you staging one of them protests?
l's staging a wet T-shirt contest.
You hang around a while,
and you might just get to judge.
And there it was...
The very first nipple
the Sheriff had ever seen.
Shove this in your eyeballs.
lnterestingly enough, it was also
the first lawn sprinkler he had ever seen.
So between the nipple
and the lawn sprinkler...
the glistening young
deputy sheriff became a man.
l'm free! l'm free!
- Rusty, l am your daddy.
- Oh, you think?
Oh, yeah. Yeah, just look at the shape
of our eyes. Exactly the same.
Krystal, l suppose
we ought to get married.
- What for?
- Come on.
You and l both know
what happened, hmm?
About 15 years ago on this very spot.
You made me play pattycake.
Unprotected pattycake.
This has happened, son.
Well, now, la di da.
Howdy doody to you, Krystal.
- Early.
- lt's been many years, but you...
- You ain't moved a bit.
- Be respectful now.
This woman here
is the mother of my child.
Your child? Hell, no.
This here is my boy.
And yeah, that's his mama.
But you, you're probably
the one that had the sexuals with her.
l refuse to touch the soft,
creamy, plump...
Damn!
Get your filthy squid hands
off of my hinter land.
l love you. l'll kill you, bitch!
- Early?
- No, Daddy, no!
l told you, Rusty.
l'm your baby daddy.
- Daddy.
- Sheriff.
There's only one way
to capture the elusive bunfish.
- Ain't that what you was talking about?
- No.
We were discussing
this boy's paternity.
l couldn't hear 'cause l was down there.
Whose bicycle is this?
Rusty? Piss on that there rabbit.
lf he dies, l'm your daddy.
Early, there's more scientific ways
of doing this.
Do it anyway.
So, we'll apply a presecreted bladder fluid
to the exoderm of this furry mammal...
and we'll look for signs of mortification
or terminalicity of the affected region.
So l'm gonna need
a urine sample from you and you.
Well, l pee sitting down.
Any approach you choose is fine.
Excuse me, sir?
Sir, not in my plastic ficus, please. lt's...
Relax, brainiac.
l filled your jar up.
My goodness!
This looks to be...
about 80 proof
straight bourbon whiskey.
Give it back!
Wait a minute.
Congratulations.
Somebody's pregnant.
Actually, doctor, we're here to find out
who the daddy is.
Of who? This rabbit?
This is dead.
No, not the rabbit.
The boy there.
l'm afraid science
can't tell us everything, little man.
- Now, that's interesting.
- What?
This rabbit's been hit by a hammer.
Well, let me get
my vaporologist in here.
Dr. Bug, get in here.
This rabbit's been hit by a hammer.
Yep. Sure has.
ls that why you dragged me in here?
Dr. Bug, have a look at these various
smokes and vapors.
- Do you see what l'm seeing?
- l reckon so, yeah, and all them.
Your young un over there
is an only child.
lf it's purple, doesn't it mean
he has a twin brother?
Shut the ... up, man!
Only child. You're an only child.
Squids!
You're a squid, right?
Shut the ... up, Jerry.
Only child. Only child.
No twin. Only child.
Man, l should be outlawed.
Subtitles by
BloodLogic
www.tvsubtitles.net