% My dreams are all dead and buried %
% Sometimes l wish the sun
would just explode %
% When God comes
and calls me to His kingdom %
% l'll take all you sons of bitches
when l go %
- My turn.
- Hell, no.
- Man, let me drive that thing. Come on!
- Do not touch the trim!
Naw, l don't need no lnternet.
No, sir. Not in my life.
- What's that, daddy?
- Rusty, what do you think of white people?
Well, l... l reckon they OK.
l likey my Doobie Brothers.
- He ain't ready.
- That's not rightly fairly.
We all was loving Doobie Brothers.
Yeah, hell,
l reckon you right.
Damn them Doobies
and they Chinese Grove.
Russell, are you ready
for the special night tonight?
What we gonna do?
Go down to Atlanta and whip our shirts off,
start a bunch of bullness?
Nope. Funner than that.
You heard what she said. Now, go ahead
and put your arm up right here.
- Why do l gotta do that for, Daddy?
- Witches be gone from his body!
My will hath been done.
We ain't driving
no witches from his body.
Well, it's done.
Tonight's good old
Tuesday's Hate White Rally.
Look at my hand, Daddy.
- Yeah, l see that.
- lt hurts.
Well, y'all need me, l'll be putting
pictures of my ass on the lnternet.
Lil, you ain't gonna come out
and hate the whites with us?
We gonna roast some weenies.
Well, la dee damn da.
All right, then, where was we at?
Give us the strength
to cleanse the Earth...
of the milk chalk scourge
so they keep 'em away from me.
Dump 'em on the island!
Blow up the island.
Look ye upon this cash money
a symbol of the white power...
who would jingle the smartest fool
with metally money.
- Burn all the metally money!
- Burn it now!
- All right, now, Granny. Burn your money.
- No, thank you.
And these skis,
tools of their wicked recreational activities.
Chalk men skiing on his white
snow in his tighty whites...
just like a white wing dove
sing a song about what they singing.
- Hoo, baby, hoo, baby, hoo!
- Light the damn skis.
That a boy, Rusty! Burn them
son-a-bitches. Embrace the hatred.
They live in houses,
don't they, Daddy?
Burn the damn house!
Guess white people
do live in houses.
Hot damn, what about
these trees over here?
- What about these trees, Granny?
- No, the trees are fine.
- Burn the damn trees.
- Burn them!
Look, everyone!
lt's the creature from the prophecy.
Naw, it's just me.
Help me, Obi Wan,
you're my only hope.
For luck. Get it?
Star Wars?
Ain't this the sci-fi convention?
Enter the circle of fire
and answer the inquisitation.
Answer the inquisitation.
Stop those drums, Kevin!
Tell me, Sheriff. What do you...
What do you think of white people?
Well, they're all right, l guess.
l mean, l like them Doobie Brothers.
Doobies aside.
Doobies has been desquawkified. All right?
Actually, Early,
l really don't mind whites so much.
l mean, some of my best friends are white.
Like me. l'm white.
- You what to the what now?
- Did l mention that to you boys?
Hey, look. See?
White as a Vidalia onion
and twice as sweet.
- Oh, no.
- Denial! Denial!
l have done deceptified
by a Sheriff with ognorance.
Burn the Sheriff.
ls that what this is all about?
A Hate White rally?
Well, it don't have to be just whites.
l mean, we're all inclusive here,
except for them damn whites.
Why do you squids
hate whites so bad?
Typical. Whitey needs
an explanation for every damn thing.
- Hey, Sheriff, where's your skis?
- Yeah, Chalky loves to ski, don't he?
Early, we're all the same
on the inside.
Here, take a look.
Up my butt.
l've had some pain recently.
- You see anything?
- A lot of red.
What happened
to the damn house?!
That there's a symbol
of the evil white chalky man, Daddy.
- lt's a symbol of where l keep my ... son!
- l'll tell you something...
and l'll say it right now with my mouth
and it needs to be listen-ded.
Whites is too deflective...
with their sheeny skin
beating sunlight into my eyes.
Can't tell them apart,
looking like lightbulbs with shoes on...
all be-bopping around all over the place.
Except for you, Sheriff.
You one of the good ones.
- Oh, yeah. You one of the good ones.
- Thank you, ma'am.
'Cause you got a gun.
Now, Sheriff,
unless you come up here to sexotize...
humpify or bangulate my grandma...
then l suggest you turn
your pretty little whitey wagon around...
and get on back to chalky town.
l will, Early.
But before l go...
l'm going to tell you where society
would be without the white man.
Eli Whitney, the inventor of the cotton gin.
A white man.
How about Crawford Long?
He discovered ether,
when he wasn't busy being white.
And you know that Sphinx in
the ancient pyramids of Egypt?
- Who do you think built those, Rusty?
- l don't know. Chalkasians?
Actually, no.
But they were in charge, probably.
Any fans of basketball out there?
Here's a name.
Larry Bird.
The inventor of the slam dunk.
That's a signature white move.
Look it up.
Rusty, you know the rap music?
l know N.W.A.
% The police going straight
from the underground %
% l don't like a brother
'cause he's brown %
Well, those ''N''s wouldn't
have any ''A'' at all...
if it wasn't for the white police state.
ln fact, all music:
rock, R&B, gospel, even reggae...
descended from,
you guessed it, whites.
So, now what do you think?
How you like me now?
What about slavery?
Who abolished it?
A white man, thank you.
But didn't you whip 'em and stuff?
Rusty, if it weren't for us whites,
your land right over here...
would be completely
overrun by red lndians.
Hell, no.
Not this land, red man!
And your Granny over there?
She'd be plunking her life savings...
into $5 slots
at a Cherokee Casino and Spa...
watching Jay Leno perform
for two weeks this October...
followed
by the Beach Boys featuring Mike Love.
Silence the lies!
Why do things have to change?
We've been hating whites
since Jesus was a june bug.
Granny, even he was a white man.
Here, take a look
at this novelty plastic Jesus.
Go ahead.
Pull his sandals.
Gotcha!
- Now get on back to your teepees!
- Folks, my point is this.
- Whites.
- Oh, Jesus. You're white? ls this true?
Yes, child. lt is l, Jesus.
And you know what?
Whether you are white, black,
Asian, or Hispanic...
we are all the same in spirit.
Except for me. l'm pretty amazing.
- Check it out. Was this your card?
- No, Lord.
- How about this one?
- Nope.
- Then it must be this one.
- Naw.
- OK, can l do it from the top?
- Have you ever done this trick before?
They're stuck is what it is,
and it's hard to... Was this your card?
- No.
- Gonna try it one more time, child of mine.
- Was this your card?
- No.
- Was it... Was it diamonds?
lt wouldn't be a trick
if l told you that.
- Three of hearts.
- No.
No. Oh, Lord, no.
No, that ain't it, either.
No, Lord. Now, see, that's the joker.
That shouldn't even be in the deck.
lt's the five of diamonds, Jesus.
lt's always the damn five of diamonds.
There we go!
Hurray, magic Jesus!
Did he say anything
different this time?
He says we all gotta love our brother.
ln other words, no.
Thank you, white Jesus!
Early, ain't no whites
ever bothered you.
l guess you're just hating
for the sake of hating.
lt ain't that, Sheriff.
lt's something else.
She was my dream, my muse...
a vision suitable
for the wide screen format.
l can still taste
her fist against my face.
The sweet sugary sweat
from a lifetime of diabetes.
A heartbeat you could hear
from six blocks away...
one big pump ev'ry hour.
These ain't glazed.
These are powdered cake.
You brainless chugnut.
You can't even get a donut right.
No, no! l can't tell him. l can't!
Get off my ass, demon love!
Douse the pain.
Tell me what, Daddy?
Santa Claus is dead!
- Your mama's white.
- Oh, my God!
She's fat as hell, too.
Subtitles by
BloodLogic
www.tvsubtitles.net